banipreet kaur

Delhi, India



banipreetkaur31@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/banipreet-kaur-0089b321a

Summary

Experienced Art Educator with a demonstrated history of working in the e-learning industry. Skilled in Business Planning, Cooking, Performing Arts, English, and Management. Strong education professional with a Commerce with business maths focused in Commerce from Adarsh Vidyalaya High School - India.

Experience



Campaign Manager

Freelance

Jul 2022 - Present (9 months)

Business Owner

IBakeYouEat

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Art Educator

Fundoo Class - Let's Learn Fundamentals; Connecting Kids To Inspiring Teachers Worldwide

Aug 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Teacher

Tuition bag private limited

Sep 2022 - Mar 2023 (7 months)

Art Educator

LearnArt

Jun 2021 - Mar 2023 (1 year 10 months)

Calligraphy Teacher

Artist Mela

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 (2 months)

Digital Marketing Intern

Swago

Dec 2021 - Mar 2022 (4 months)

Muman Resources Intern

Unschool

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021 (2 months)

(6) Human Resources Intern

Swago

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Sales And Marketing Intern

Universal Tribes

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021 (2 months)

Marketing Intern

MeetMeFit

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021 (2 months)

- 1. Engaging with the Social Media Posts and promotion.
- 2. Market Research With respect to the Product.
- 3. Developing marketing Strategies.
- 4. Usage of app's features.
- 5. Achieving your own personal goal.

Fundraising Intern

Muskurahat Foundation

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021 (2 months)

-Your main task is to raise funds for the NGO by approaching people in your personal connections. Basically, you will be raising funds through your network, which is your friends, family, relatives, colleagues, classmates, relatives, etc

You will be trained in the following fields-

You will learn how to run a successful campaign under our expertise.

NGO Funding

Leveraging your network

Marketing techniques

How NGO functions and how you can create an impact.

Youth influencer

Unschool

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

Sales and Marketing of the courses

Art Educator

Learn infinity

May 2021 - Jul 2021 (3 months)

Education

Sri Guru Tegh Bahadur Khalsa College

Bachelor's degree Oct 2021 - Oct 2024

Adarsh Vidyalaya High School - India

Higher Education, Commerce Jun 2019 - Jun 2021

S S MOTA SINGH MODEL SCHOOL

Primary and Secondary Education 2009 - 2019

Skills

English • Arts & Crafts • Performing Arts • Baking • Cooking • Communication • Teaching • Leadership • Paper Craft • E-Learning